Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Louden, Sharon, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Loughran, Daniel, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Love, Robyn, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Lovelace, Simon, undated (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Lovitt, Sarah, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Lowenthal, Joanne, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Lowery, Christopher, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Lowery, Stephen, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Lowther, Rachel, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Lowy, Diane, 1999-2005 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Lozano Luviano, Gabriela, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Lubelski, Nava, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Lubliner, Barbara, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Lucente, Jenna, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Luckring, Eve, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Ludavicius, Julius, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- Luib, Tony, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Lujan, Jason, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Luken, Deborah, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 55)
- Lukenskas, Ceslovas, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Lume, CM, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 57)
- Lund, Birgitta, 1993-1999 (Box 32, Folder 58)
- Lund-Torroll, Cynthia, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Lundsfryd, Tine, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Luner, Karin, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Lupo, Maria, 1990-1998 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Lurye, Helen, 1990-2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Lusk, Matthew, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Lust, Janet, 1987-2001 (Box 64, Folder 75)
- Lusmila, Elisabeth, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Lutzker, Emily, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Lydecker, Mary, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Lyle, Gordon, Jamie, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Lynam, Anne, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Lynch, Mindy, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Lynch, Rene, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Lyons, Rosemary, 1991-1998 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Lyshak, Francie, 1997-2002 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Mabbett, Rachel, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- MacDonald, Ellen, 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Macdonald, Rita, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Machado, Thessia, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Machell, Iain, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Machida, Chie, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Mackenzie, David, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Mackey, Michelle, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Mackey, Roy, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Mackler, Alice, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Mackler, Lauren, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- MacRae, Alisdair, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Maddocks, Chris, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Maenak, Kim, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Maeng, Jee-Young, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Maertz, Allen, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Magdo, Michele, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Magliozzi, Roberto, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Magne, Marianne, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Magnotta, Francis, 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Magpantay Triplitt, Gilberto, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Magsamen, Mary, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Maher, Caroline, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Maher, James, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Maher, Mary Kate, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Maher, Richard, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Mahoney, Brian, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Maida, Joseph, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Major, Rebecca, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Major, Shawne, 2000-2005 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Mak, Elim, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Maki, Maureen, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Makov, Paul, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Maksymowicz, Virginia, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Malakoff, Sarah, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Maldari, Domenick, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Malewska, Monika, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 51)
- Malinow, Phyllis, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 52)
- Malitz, Suzanne, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Mallo, Luis, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 55)
- Malloizel, Anne, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 56)
- Maloff, Chalda, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 54)
- Malone, Katy, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 57)
- Man, Victor, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 59)
- Manders, Susan, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 58)
- Mangrum, Virginia, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 60)
- Mann, Valerie, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 61)
- Manning, Stephen, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Mannis, Josh, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Mantell, Eva, 1992-2001 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Manuel, Brenna, 1996-2001 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Mar, Alex, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Marangoni, Emiliano, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Maranz, Bonnie, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Marburg, Charles, 1997-2002 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Marcano, Soraya, 1995-2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Marchan, Javier, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Marchand, Anne, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Marchand, Francois, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Marco, Mitchell, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Mardin, Julie, 1996-2004 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Mardyks, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Marella, Marco, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Margaryan, Hovhannes, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Margolis, Aimee, 1991-2000 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Margolis, Karen, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Margolis, Valerie, 1994-2002 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Mari, Eduardo, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Maria, Kara, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Mariano, Joseph, 1994-2002 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Mariano, Linda, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Marion, Harriet, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Markel, Freda, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Markell, Eliot, 1986-2004 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Markelson, Zana, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Markham, Walter, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Markman, Grace, 1993-2002 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Markell,Eliot, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Markman, Lori, 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Marks, Arthur, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Marks, Joshua R., 2005 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Marks, Melissa, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Marks, Terry, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Marlatt, Megan, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Marmorek, Rochelle, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Marr, Aliyah, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Marsching, Jane, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Marshall, Barry, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Marshall, Donna, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Marshall, Jeffrey, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Marshall, Lee, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Marshall, Robert, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Marston, Heidi, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- Marston, Karen, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Martha, Tirzo, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 54)
- Martin, Greg, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Martin, Jean-Marie, 1996-2000 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- Martin, Juliet, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Martin, Katy, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Martin, Timothy Michael, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- Martin, Rebecca, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- Martin, Tony, 1994-2001 (Box 34, Folder 53)
- Martin, William, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Martineau, Sam, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Martinelli, Diana, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Martinez, Rossana, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Martirosyan, Arshak, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Martonis, Stephen, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Marx, Kristine, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Maryschuk, Olga, 1988-2005 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Masahiro, Amano, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Masley, Caitlin, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Maslen, Tim, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Mason, Jeanette, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Massry, Vivian, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Masuyama, Shiro, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Maszk, Michael, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Mata, Ben, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Mathias, Thelma, 1989-2001 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Matlaga, Douglas, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Matos-Capote, Juan, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Matsuda-Dunn, Pamela, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Mattera, Joanne, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Matsuda-Dunn, Pamela, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Matsumoto, Harutaka, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Matthews, Amanda, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Matthews-Lawrence, Kegera, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Mattingly, Mary, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Matyjewicz, Heath, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Maun, Patrick, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Maxwell, Barry, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- Maxwell, Brookie, 1991-2005 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Maxwell, Brookie, 1991-2005 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Maxwell, Kathryn, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- Mayo, Sherry, 1995-1999 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Mazza, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Mazzalupo, Christina, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Mazzella, Marcello, 1994-1997 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Mazzetti, Laetitia, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- McAree, Francoise, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- McBean, Michael, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- McBee, Ned, 1992-1997 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- McCabe, Richard, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- McCaffrey, Michael, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- McCagg, Alexandra, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- McCambridge, Anna, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- McCann, Margaret, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- McCarron, Maureen, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- McCauley, Frank, undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
- McClean, Karen, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- McClintock, Jane, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- McClutcheon, Brian, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- McClure, Steve, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- McCluskey, Corrie, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- McCollister, Todd, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 48)
- McConaughy, Claire, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 49)
- McConnell, Julie A., 1999-2004 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- McConnell, Walter, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- McDaniel, Harry, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- McDonald, Jillian, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- McDowell, Katherine, 1998-2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- McGinnis, Susanne, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- McGlynn, David, 1981-1997 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- McGrath, Mary, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- McIlveen, Francis, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- McKay, Joe, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- McKinley, Carl M., 2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- McLaren, Fiona, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- McLaughlin, Tricia, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- McLennon, Carol, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- McLeod, Emily, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- McMahon, Jeff, 2001-2003 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- McMahon, Tara, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- McManus, Darren, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- McManus, James, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- McMorrow, Denise, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- McNabb, Trena, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- McNally, Susan, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- McNeal, Meridith, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- McNichol, Bernard, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- McNulty, Christopher, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- McNulty, Sarah E., 2003 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- McPherson, Iain, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- McQuillan, Maureen, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- McRaven, Kelly, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Mead, Stephen, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Medal, Kevin, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Medeiros- Muller, Flevia, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Medina, Chris, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Mednick, Arthur, 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Meehan, Alisoun, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Meehan, Suzanne, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Meier, Jacqueline, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Meimaroglou, Despina, 1986-1992 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Meisel, Sandra, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Melamed, Brad, 1994-2001 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Melander, Derick, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Melas, Eva, 1992-1998 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Melchionne, Kevin, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Meledandri, Nina, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Meledachri, Nina, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- Melhado, Paul Anthony, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Melin, Kristin, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Meller, Sonja, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Melody, Owen, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Meloro, Anthony, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Melzmuf, Robert, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Melton, Julie, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Mender, Donald, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Meneses, Juanita, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 50)
- Mensing, Margo, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Meredith, Virginia, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 53)
- Merenmies, Elina, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 52)
- Merges, Palmarin, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Merians, Valerie, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Merinoff, Leigh, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Merinoff, Leigh, 1993-1999 (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Merlis, Annette, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Merrell, Clayton, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Merrell, James, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Merrick, Tim, 1991-2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Mesa-Gaido, Elisabeth, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Mesa, Nilda, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Meson, Dawn, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Messerschmidt, Andy, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Metal, Camilla, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Metz, Georgia, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Mew, Tommy, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Meyer, Diane, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Meyer, Elizabeth, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Meyers, Andrea, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Meyers, Charles, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Meyers, Jeff, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Meyers, Justin, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Meylan, Clement-Olivier, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Meza, Abinadi, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Mezynski, Neila, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Miceli, Patrick, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Michael, Creighton, 1992-2002 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Michalakakos, Maro, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Michals, Robin, 1996-2005 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Middlebrook, Jason, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Migliore-Newton, Kathleen, 1996-2005 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Mikalsen, Kent, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Miles, Eric, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Millar, Steven, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Millennium, Meps, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Miller, Catherine, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Miller, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Miller, Hank, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Miller, Jessica, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Miller, Matt, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Mitchell, Megan, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Miyazi, Hiroshi, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Mladenoff, Nancy, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Mladenoff, Nancy, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Moderbacher, Eileen Starr, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Moderegger, Hajoe, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Modiano, Jim, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Modrak, Judith, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Mohan, Monica, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Mohn, Anja, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- mokomoko, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Molina, Hernando, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Molly, Michael, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Mon, Bascha, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Monaghan, Kellyann, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Monastra, Carolyn, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Moncier, Mimi, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Monick, Jenny, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Moninger, James, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Montalvo, Edwin, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Montgomery, Heath, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Montgomery, Melinda, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Montoya, Daniel, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Mooibroek, Eveline, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Moon, Grace, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Moonelis, Judy, 1982-1989 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Mooney, Michael, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Moore, Christine, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Moore, Cindy, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Moore, Heather B., 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Moore, Matthew, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Moore, Natalie, 1990-1997 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Moore, Norman E., 1985-1991 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Moores, James, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Moosreiner, Mari, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Mora, Marie Herman, 1990-1993 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Moran, Andrew, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Moran, Donna, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Moran, Kate, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Moran, Tom, 2000-2003 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Mordhorst, Lisa, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Moreau, Jeff, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Moreira, David, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Morgan, Willard, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Morganstern, Andrea, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Moriarty, Laura, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Morin, Ricardo, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Morioka, Juri, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Morita, Eri, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Moriyama, Tadashi, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Morris, Dean, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Morris, Deborah, 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Morris, Jim, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Morrison, J., 2005 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Morrison, Joel, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Morrison, John, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Morrison, Mandy, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Morrison, Rachael, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Mortimer, Dylan, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Moseley, Wayne, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Moseley, Wayne, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Moseni, Arezoo, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Moses, Micah, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Mosher, Eve S., 2003 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Moskowitz, Carolyn, 1991-1995 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Moss, Karen, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Moss, Kathy, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Mosse, Gerard, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Mota, Joao, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Mottai, Laura, 1994-1998 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Mount, Jane, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Mousis, Panagiota, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Moycik-Aguilera, Mary, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Moyer, Carrie, 1994-2003 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Moyer, Sheldon, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Mozman, Rachelle, 1998-2001 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Mrozowski, Ryan, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Muel, Susanne, 1988-1998 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Mueller, Joan, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Mueller, Regi, 1992-2000 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Muirhead, Deborah, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Mukerjee, Brian, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Mullan, Colette, 1989-1993 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Mullan, Eileen, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Mullaney, Peter, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Muller, Jessica, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Mulligan, Colleen, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Mulone, Rosella, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Mumford, Steve, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Mumm, Denise, 1987-1993 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Munizaga, Alejandra, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Munk, Loren, 1996-2000 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Munoz, Susan, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Muraczewski, Christina, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Murphy, Ann Bridget, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Murphy, Bill, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Murphy, Joel, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 99)
- Murphy, Margaret, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Murphy, Margaret, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 77)
- Murphy, Mark, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Murphy, Rita, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 48)
- Murphy, Tomasita, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Murray, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Murray, Katie, 2000-2003 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Murray, Tim, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Murtaugh, Rebecca, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- Musovic, Tafil, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Mussman, Toby, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Musson, Amanda, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Muster, Michael, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Musumeci, Costanza, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Mut, Michael, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Mutzel, Timothy, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- Myer, Georgia, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 47)
- Myers, Kristin, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Mylonas, Eleni, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Nachman, Kirk, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- Nadeau, Jessica, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 52)
- Nadeau, Joelle, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 53)
- Nadel, Alfred, 1994-2000 (Box 38, Folder 54)
- Nadelhaft, Edith, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 55)
- Nadzieja, Elisa, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 56)
- Naegele, Cushla, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 46)
- Nagahiro, Emiko, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 57)
- Nagamatsu, Ryuji, 1989-1994 (Box 62, Folder 45)
- Nagamori, Toshie, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Nagaoka, Linda, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 58)
- Nagorka, Stefanie, 1991-1995 (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Nahon, Brigitte, 1990-1994 (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Nakagawa, Reina, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 59)
- Nakamura, Hiroyuki, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Nakamura, Yuki, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 60)
- Nakane, Seiji, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Nakazato, Shinya, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 61)
- Nam, Hyo-Jeong, 1990-2004 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Namekawa, Misa, 1998-2003 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Namie, Math-You, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 62)
- Nanderyken, Philip, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Nangle, Karen, 1998-2001 (Box 38, Folder 63)
- Napierala, Jim, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 64)
- Napolitano, Domenico, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 65)
- Naponic, Anthony, 1979-1989 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Narahashi, Keiko, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 66)
- Nash, Kirsten, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 67)
- Nath, Heather, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 68)
- Nathan, Piotr, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 69)
- Natsoulas, Anthony, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 70)
- Nau, Sharol, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 71)
- Neal, Florence, 1985-1988 (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Neary, Scott, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 72)
- Neblett, Marcia, 1994-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Neckles, Shervone, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Neely, Jennifer, 1985-1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Neff, Stacey, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Negoro, Kazuko, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Nei, Barbara, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Neider, Alan, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Neill, Margaret, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Neilson, Heidi, 1998-2001 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Nelson, Aida, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Nelson, Chad, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Nelson, Jen, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Nelson, Michael, 1991-2001 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Nemesh, Magdalena, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Nemkova, Elena, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Nesbitt, Sara, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Nesgoda, Nika, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Ness, Karena, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Neubauer, Brandon, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Neunhoeffer, Susanne, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Neveaux, Octavius, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Newberry, Michael, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Newell, Carlo, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Newman, Aaron, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Newman, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Newmark, Alexandra, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Newsom, Becky, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Newton, Douglas, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Ng, Annysa, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Nguyen, Christian, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Nguyen, Khang, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Nguyen, Phuong, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Nguyen, Stephen B., 2002 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Nguyen, Trong, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Nguyen, UuDam, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Nicholas, Trever, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Nicholls, Sarah, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Nichols, Garry, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Nicholson, Mary, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Nickard, Christopher, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Nickel, James, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Nickel, Jason, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Nicol, Janet, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Nicola, Ion, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Nicolai, Thomas, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Nicoletta, Sandrine, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Nicoll, Ruth, undated (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Niemeyer, Andre, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Nieves, Meredith, 1988-1992 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Niewierski, Kortney K., 2006 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Nigro, Lisa, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Nigro, Samuel, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Niklewicz, Adam, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Nilsson, Sophia, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Nirenberg, Michael, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Nishijima, Atsushi, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Nishino, Sachiko, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Nishiyama, Jiro, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Niss, Jodie, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Nitsche, Martina, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Nix, Lori, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Nobel, Lindsey, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Nobre, Luis, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Noftsinger, Pamela, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Nofziger, Liz, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Noguchi, Yasushi, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 57)
- Nolan, Jim, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Nolan, Sean, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Nolan, Timothy, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Nolan, Yumiko, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 61)
- Noland, Garry, 1997-2004 (Box 39, Folder 62)
- Norcross, James, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 63)
- Norkin, Michael, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 64)
- Normal Group, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 65)
- Norman-Hayes, Tiffany, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 66)
- Nornberg, Moses, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 67)
- Novick, Steve, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 68)
- Nowak, Susan, 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 53)
- Nozawa, Fumiko, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Nuccio Llewellyn, Jennifer, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Nuell, Christie, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Nuno, Domingo, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Nurkse, Lucille, 1999-2004 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- O'Brien, Dermot, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- O'Brien, William John, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- O'Connell, Hilda, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 53)
- O'Connor, John, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- o'Hara slavick, elin, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 51)
- O'Malley, J.M., 2005 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- O'Rourke, Janell, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- O'Shaughnessy, John, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- O'Shaughnessy, Vivian, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 46)